Hi.
Hey.
So, what's the final head count
on my baby shower?
About 20.
A couple people from work
who had something else to do.
Both of your
sisters called
and neither can make it.
What? You mean
they're not coming
to a social event where
there's no men and no booze?
That's shocking!
Well, I don't care.
As long as my mom's here.
Oh, my God-- your mother.
What, my mom's
not going to be here?
Well, given that
we forgot to invite her
it would be an awfully big
coincidence if she was.
My God!
It wasn't my fault.
Phoebe was in charge
of invitations.
Well, I don't,
I don't have a mother
so often I forget that...
Oh, give it a rest.
So, my mother is not coming
to my baby shower?
No.
Neither is mine.
Hey, you know what?
Don't worry, okay?
We'll take care of it.
We'll call her.
You just go home
and get ready.
Please make sure
she comes.
It's really important
to me.
I mean, it's my mom.
I know, I know.
What's her number?
I don't know.
Go. I have it in my book.
Go.
( door shuts )
Wait a minute.
If you're in charge
of invitations
why am I the one
who has to call her?
Hello, Mrs. Green.
Hi. Uh, it's Monica Geller.
Oh, hello, Monica.
Hi, um,
I know this is last minute
but we've decided to throw
an impromptu
baby shower
for Rachel today.
I know.
My daughters told me about it
when they received
their impromptu invitations
a month ago.
( weak chuckle )
Okay, I'm sorry.
I-I'm so sorry.
For what, dear?
For not inviting me,
or for lying about it?
Oh, my God, my ass is sweating.
Oh, please, please...
can you come?
It's today at 4:00.
Well, all right.
I'll see you at 4:00.
Thank you.
Isn't it at 3:00?
Son of a bitch!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Joe,
want to shoot some hoops?
Oh, I can't go.
I'm practicing.
I got an audition
to be the host
of a new game show.
Oh, cool!
That's great.
Yeah, yeah, and if I get it,
by day, I'll be
( lowers voice ):
Dr. Drake Remoray
but by night, I'll be
( loud and excited ):
Joey Tribbiani!
You'll be perfect
for this.
That's already your name.
The audition's
in a couple of hours
and I don't even understand
the game.
Well, do you
want some help?
Really? That would be great.
Hey, you guys
could be the contestants.
Awesome.
Okay, I guess we can lose
to junior high girls
some other time.
All right--
let's play Bamboozled!
Bamboozled?
Yeah, isn't that
a cool name?
Yeah.
No.
All right.
Uh, okay.
Our first contestant
is Ross Geller.
Why don't you tell us
a little bit
about yourself, Ross?
Well, uh
I-I'm a
paleontologist.
Um, I-I live
in New York.
I have a son, Ben.
Uh, hi, Ben.
And, uh...
I said
a little bit, Ross.
Now, how about you, Chandler?
Well, Joey,
I'm a headhunter.
I hook up
out-of-work Soviet scientists
with rogue Third World nations.
Hi, Rasputin.
Excellent. Let's play
Bamboozled.
Chandler,
you'll go first.
"What is the capital
of Colombia?"
Bogota.
It's "Bagoda,"
but close enough.
Uh... now,
oh, now
you can either pass
your turn to Ross
or pick a Wicked
Wango card.
What does
a Wicked Wango card do?
I should know that.
Let's see-- just
one moment, please.
Um... here we are.
"A Wicked Wango card
determines whether
you go higher or lower."
Higher or lower than what?
( phony host voice ):
This is embarrassing.
Can you believe
how lame this is?
I'm sorry,
I don't believe contestants
are allowed
to talk to each other.
Oh, I told the stripper
to be here at 5:00.
That's good, right?
You ordered a stripper
for the shower?
That is totally
inappropriate.
Why? He's going to be dressed
as a baby.
Oh, hi, Mrs. Green.
I'm so glad you
could make it.
Yes, thank you so much.
And again,
we're so sorry.
We could not feel worse
about it.
Try.
Oh, there's my little girl.
She's still mad.
Yeah, I know.
Isn't it great--
one less person
we have to make
small talk with?
Phoebe, Sandra's mad
at you, too.
It doesn't bother you?
Well, we've
apologized twice
and I can't do
any more than that.
I know you hate it when
people are mad at you
but, you know, you just
have to be okay with it.
Okay. I can do that.
( chuckling )
I got to go powder my ass.
Look at that face.
Just like when you
were in high school.
If I didn't know better
I'd say you were a
cheerleader in trouble.
( both chuckling )
Come on, let's
get some tea.
My, look at that.
Only three weeks to go.
Now, have you picked
your nanny yet?
Now, honey, I don't
want you to just
use your housekeeper
'cause it will just
split her focus.
Oh, well, actually
I'm not going to use a nanny
and, uh, I don't even have
a housekeeper.
It's like you're
a cave person.
Rachel
you must get a nanny.
You don't know
how overwhelming
this is going to be.
I mean, when
you were a baby
I had full-time help--
I had Mrs. Kaye.
Mrs. Kaye--
oh, she was sweet.
She taught me Spanish.
I actually think
I remember some of it.
Tu madre es loca.
Such a sweet woman.
Yeah.
Well, however great she was,
I just can't afford that.
Oh, Rachel!
What?
I just had the
greatest idea.
I'm going to come
live with you.
Wh-Wh-What? What?
Oh, I'm so happy
I'm going to do this
for my little girl.
Oh, look at you.
You have tears
in your eyes.
Yes, yes, I do.
All right, Ross,
you're in the lead.
Would you like
to take another question
or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
The Wheel has not been
my friend tonight, Joey.
Uh... I'll take
another question.
Okay. This is going
to be tough.
Hold your breath.
It's okay;
I'm ready.
No, dude,
you got to hold your breath
till you're ready
to answer the question.
It's part
of the game.
This is
ridiculous.
He's not
going to...
( inhaling loudly )
Okay.
"What do you have a fear of
"if you suffer
from this phobia?
Tris... ka..."
Holy cow,
that's a big word.
"Trisk..."
Seriously,
look at this thing.
Chandler,
how do you say that?
Let me see that.
This one right here.
( high-pitched mumble )
"Triskaidekaphobia."
( loud exhale ):
Fear of Triscuits.
No, fear of the number 13.
Fear of Triscuits?
It's possible.
They have really sharp edges.
All right, Chandler,
you're up.
Wait a minute.
I believe I'm entitled
to use my Angel Pass
for a free turn.
This game makes no sense!
You know,
you're just upset
'cause you're losing.
Oh, come on, Ross.
I think we're all losers here.
All right, Chandler
you can either
spin the wheel
or pick a Google card.
Let me think,
let me think.
Oh, uh, I don't care.
( chuckling )
You must choose,
Mr. Bing.
Either.
It makes no difference.
Choose, you jackass.
I'll take a card.
Okay.
You picked
the Gimme card.
You get all of
Ross's points.
What?!
This game is kind of fun.
You don't think
it's a little crazy
that you get
all my points...?
I don't think the contestants
are supposed to speak
to each other.
Why did you invite my mother?!
What?
She wants to move in
with me and Ross
to help take care of the baby.
For how long?
Eight weeks.
I mean, I
love my mother
but, my God, a
long lunch with
her is taxing.
I personally
would be honored
if she wanted
to live with me.
She can't hear you.
You guys, come on,
what am I going to do?
Well, if you don't want
your mother to move in with you
just tell her.
You're right. You're right.
I mean,
I'm about to have a baby.
I can tell my mother
that I don't want her
to be sleeping on my couch.
Oh, my God, she's going to want
to sleep in my bed with me.
This cannot happen.
That's right.
That is right.
You go over there
and tell her
you do not want her
to live with you.
Do not take no
for an answer.
Okay.
This is great.
Now she's going
to be mad at Rachel.
You know what?
And I'm just going
to swoop in there
and be like the daughter
she never had.
I have new respect
for Chandler.
All right, everybody,
it's time to open the presents!
Yes, yes, and I think
that the first gift
that Rachel opens
should be from the
grandmother of the baby.
Because you're the
most important person
in this room.
And in the world.
Well, uh, I don't have a gift
because I wasn't invited
until the last minute
but thank you so much, dear
for bringing that
to everybody's attention.
How about
you less important people?
Let's open your presents.
Hey, Mom, that's okay
that you didn't get me a gift.
Well, I kind of did. Me.
Eight weeks of me.
Yeah. Okay, see, Mom,
the truth is
I can do this on my own.
Sweetheart
I know you're going
to be a terrific mom.
I just think you
need a little help
especially at the beginning.
But, Mom, I really know
what I'm doing.
I can handle this.
Really? Remember Twinkles?
He was a hamster.
I am not going
to vacuum up my baby.
Okay
come on, Rach.
It's present time.
You know, you're the glue
holding this whole party
together.
It's kind of falling apart here.
Ooh, look.
Wow.
This is from
your friends at work.
Ooh! My gosh!
Oh, wow!
Oh, I know what this is.
Wait a minute.
That can't be right.
Is that a beer bong
for a baby?
Darling, that's
a breast pump.
( coughing chuckle )
Did I say
I was done guessing?
Okay, thank you for that.
Ooh, wow.
What's this?
It's a Diaper Genie.
Oh, it dispenses
clean diapers.
No, it's where
you put the dirty ones.
Well, that's gross.
Why don't you
just take it outside
and throw it
in a Dumpster?
Oh, you're going to do
that ten times a day?
What, it goes
ten times a day?!
What are we feeding
this baby, Indian food?
No, dear, that's
what babies do.
Rachel,
listen to your mother.
She is very smart.
Plus, what are you
planning on doing
with the baby
while you're trotting
out to the garbage
ten times a day?
I don't know.
Leave it on the changing table?
( women gasping )
What? What'd I do?
What'd I do?
You can't leave
a baby alone.
( sputtering )
Of course.
I know that.
I mean, of course
you never leave a baby alone.
( laughing ):
She wouldn't be safe.
You know, not as safe
as she would be with me,
the baby dummy.
Ooh, God,
okay, you know what?
Opening the presents
is a little overwhelming
right now
so I think, um,
I'm just going to maybe
open them all a little bit later
but thank you all for coming
and for these beautiful gifts
and this basket is beautiful.
It's actually a bassinet.
Okay, Mommy,
don't ever leave me.
"In what John Huston film
would you hear this line--
"'Badges? We don't need
no stinking badges'?
Treasure of
the Sierra Madre!
Correct. There's
a possible backwards bonus.
Madre Sierra the of Treasure!
Yes!
I'd like to go up
the Ladder of Chance
to the Golden
Mud Hut, please.
Wise choice.
How many rungs?
Six.
( cackles like monkey )
That noise
can only mean one thing.
Hungry monkey! Ha!
Hungry monkey.
I'd like a Wicked Wango card.
Okay.
It's an audio question.
"Name this television
theme song."
( sings I Dream
of Jeannie theme )
Oh...
Oh. Oh, my God.
Okay, I know this.
Give me a second.
Tell it to the Time Turtle!
Shut up!
I Dream of Jeannie!
Yes.
You're back
in the lead.
I'd like
to spin the wheel.
Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat...
tat... tat... tat...
tat... tat...
tat...
Oh, come on!
Uh, Super-Speedy Speed round.
Is there
a hopping bonus?
Of course.
"Who invented bifocals?"
Ben Franklin.
Correct.
"Which monarch has ruled
Great Britain the longest?"
Queen Victoria.
Correct
again.
But you forgot to switch legs
between questions
so no Hopping Bonus.
Oh! No! Every time!
Now, over to Chandler.
I'd like a Google card.
Are you sure?
Yes.
No!
Google!
Oh, my God.
Congratulations, Ross.
Because, Chandler,
you've been Bamboozled!
No!
Yes!
This is the
best game ever!
So, um, you're going
to stay with me
as long as I need you?
Of course I am.
Oh, Mom, I swear,
I'm not an idiot.
I read all kinds
of books on pregnancy
and giving birth
but I just didn't think
to read the part
about what to do
when the baby comes.
And-and... guess what--
the baby's coming
and I don't know what to do.
Oh.
Could I throw up
in my Diaper Genie?
Oh, sweetie, you're
going to be fine.
Wait, where you going?
Where you going?
I'm going to
the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
Now, don't worry.
Everything's
going to be okay.
It is going to be okay.
Worth a shot.
Hey.
Why are you all
red and sweaty?
I just Bamboozled Chandler.
Which is not a sexual thing.
That was a quick shower.
Not if you were here.
Wow, looks like we got
a lot of good stuff.
Oh, we did.
But my mom got us
the greatest gift of all.
A Play-Doh barber shop?
No.
She's going to live
with us for eight weeks.
Wh-What?
Yeah, she's going to help us
take care of the baby. Whoo.
You're not serious.
I mean, she's
a very nice woman
but there's no way we can
take eight weeks of her.
She'll drive us
totally crazy...
Hi, Ross.
Hey, roomie!
Hey, Joey, hi.
I'm Ray, I'm the
producer of the show.
( phony host voice ):
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Ray.
And this is
Duncan and Erin.
They're going help us out
with the audition.
So, let's get
the camera rolling.
Righty-o, Ray.
Whenever you're ready.
Hello, I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Let's play Bamboozled.
Erin, you get
the first question.
"In hockey,
who is known as the Great One?"
Wayne Gretzky.
Correct.
Now, would you like
to pick a Wicked Wango card
or spin the Wheel of Mayhem?
Uh, Joey, didn't your agents
give you the revised rules?
We've eliminated all that.
No wheel, no cards.
Wh-Why?
Uh, well, the game
was too complicated
and research showed
people didn't follow it.
What's complicated?
You spin the Wheel of Mayhem
to go up the Ladder of Chance
you go past the Mud Hut
through the Rainbow Ring
to get to the Golden Monkey
you yank his tail, and boom,
you're in Paradise Pond.
Yeah.
All that's gone.
It's basically just a simple
question-and-answer game now.
Well, what's fun about that?
You expect me to be the host
of some boring game
that's just people standing
around answering questions?
Well, there'll be women in
bikinis holding up the scores.
Let's play Bamboozled.
And all those dinosaur
knickknacks you have
Ross, I thought they might be
more at home in the garage.
Well, we don't
have a garage.
Did I say garage?
I meant garbage.
You know what,
Mrs. Green
maybe it's not
absolutely vital
that you live with us.
But Rachel needs help
with the baby.
I do, I really do.
I don't know anything.
I'm sure that's not true.
Oh, no?
Pheebs, Monica,
do I know anything
about babies?
Nope, not
a thing.
It's frightening.
Well, you know what
even if she doesn't
know anything, I do.
I have a son, and his mother
and I didn't live together
and whenever he was with me
I took care of him
all the time, by myself.
That's true.
You do have another child.
Yeah.
With another woman.
Have you no control, Ross?
That's a different issue.
The point is,
when the baby comes
I will be there to feed her
and bathe her and change her
and, more than that, I want
to do all those things.
Well, then you really don't
need me to live with you.
Yes!
Yes, you're going
to be so missed.
You're going to be
a great father.
Well, you're going to be
a wonderful grandma.
Hello?
I still don't know
what the hell I'm doing.
Oh, come on, every
first-time mother
feels that way.
You'll... you're going
to pick it up.
Hey, you will.
Look, you know when you
first came to the city
you were this spoiled
helpless little girl
who still used daddy's
credit cards, remember?
I hope you're going
somewhere with this.
Look at you, would you?
You're this big executive.
You are much
more capable
than you give
yourself credit for.
I have no doubt you're going
to be an incredible mother.
Really?
I'm telling you.
Thank you.
All right, you two
I'm going
to get going.
Oh, no, no,
sweetheart.
You stay put.
I'll let myself out.
It's like I'm not here.
Which I almost wasn't.
( laughs loudly )
You're still so funny.
It's so funny.
What do I do?
Nothing.
You have apologized to her,
like, a million times
and she's been nothing
but terrible to you.
And don't forget
you just threw
her daughter a lovely
albeit slightly boring,
shower.
And she hasn't even
thanked you for it.
You know what, you're right.
Yeah, I mean, if you want
to say anything to her,
I'd tell her off.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Okay, I will.
Mrs. Green.
It is rude to
leave a party
without saying
good-bye to the host.
And also, when someone
apologizes to you
the decent thing to do
is to accept it.
Because what I did to you,
it wasn't on purpose
but what you're doing to me now,
it's just plain spiteful.
Spiteful?
That's right.
Maybe it's time you
took a good hard look
in the mirror, young lady.
Old lady.
Lady.
Wrap it up, wrap it up,
wrap it up.
So, whenever you're
ready to apologize to me
I will forgive you.
Good day.
I can't feel my legs.
But you were fantastic.
I'm so proud of you.
Yeah?
I'm proud of me, too.
You should be.
Could you get me
something to drink?
You got it.
Okay.
Mrs. Green!
Okay, I'm really sorry!
I apologize!
If you could...
( screams )
( thudding )
Okay, I bit my tongue...
( lisping ):
but I'm thtill really thorry!
Okay, I'm ready.
You sure?
Yes.
I've done my studying
and I really know my stuff.
All right, then.
Rachel Green,
let's play Bamboozled.
"How do you test the temperature
of the baby's bath water?"
Uh, put your elbow in it.
Excellent.
"How do you put
a baby down for a nap?"
Full, dry, on it's back,
and no loose covers.
That's correct.
This is an audio question.
"What do you do
when the baby makes this sound?"
( high-pitched crying )
Check if it's wet,
check if it's hungry, burp it.
Excellent! Excellent!
Now, now, do you
want another question
or a Wicked Wango card?
A card, a card, I pick a card.
Oh, I'm sorry,
you've been Bamboozled.
You're going
to be a terrible mother.
( phony host voice ):
I've lost sight
of why we're doing this.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org